Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- Richard Henry Lee to Patrick Henry, 1777 April 22; No. 1967
- Robert Edward Lee to ________, 1839 November 27; No. 1968
- William Lee to Samuel Lewis Southard, 1826 July 26; No. 1969
- E.G. Leigh, 1843; No. 1970
- Jacob LeRoy to John DeWitt, Jr., No. 1971
- Betty Washington Lewis, 1785 August; No. 1972
- Betty Washington Lewis to her brother George Washington, 1792 April 19; No. 1973
- Eleanor Parke Custis Lewis to Elizabeth G.W. Butler, 1851 August 27; No. 1974
- Betty Washington? Lewis, n.d.; No. 1975
- Fielding Lewis to William Carpenter, 1783 April 1; No. 1976
- Fielding Lewis to William Carpenter, 1783 March 26; No. 1977
- Estate of Fielding Lewis, n.d.; No. 1978
- Fielding Lewis to Lawrence Lewis, 1787 November 21; No. 1979
- Estate of Fielding Lewis, 1770 June 7-1783 December 17; No. 1980
- Charles Carter to George Lewis, 1801 July 18; No. 1981
- Shays' Rebellion, 1786-1787; No. 1982
- Rev. Theophilus Lindsey to Rev. William Turner, 1774 December 15; No. 1983
- Gilbert Livingston, 1780 July 20, 23; No. 1984
- Robert R. Livingston to George Washington, 1794 April 10; No. 1985
- Robert R. Livingston to the President of the State of New Hampshire (Meshech Weare), 1782 May 14; No. 1986
- William Smith Livingston to ________, 1779 March 4; No. 1987
- Thomas Lloyd to ________, 1770 August 20; No. 1988
- Joshua Loring to George Washington, 1777 March 24; No. 1989
- Louis XVI, king of France to M. L'Amiral, 1779 April 5; No. 1990
- Louis XVI, king of France to Pierre-Francois Cornic Dumoulin, 1777 August 24; No. 1991
  See also Nos. 1850, 2059-2061.
- Solomon Lovell to David Cushing, 1776 June 12; No. 1992
- Gabriel W. Ludlow, 1780-1782; No. 1993
- William Lyles to John Fitzgerald, 1790 August 23; No. 1994
- William Lyles to John Fitzgerald, 1790 October 15; No. 1995
- New York Committee of Safety "to Every Committee and to Every Friend to Liberty in the United Colonies", 1776 March 30; No. 1996
- Peter McLauhlin to Timothy Pickering, 1783 February 10; No. 1997
- James Madison to the Purveyor of the United States (Israel Whelen), 1801 May 21; No. 1998
- James Madison to William Cabell Rives, 1828 December 2; No. 1999
- James Madison to John Drayton, 1821 September 23; No. 2000
- Charles Magill to Lawrence Lewis, 1792 December 28; No. 2001
- State of Maryland, Baltimore County Grand Jury, 1780 March 15; No. 2002
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Attorney General (Robert Treat Paine)to the Justices of the Inferior Court of Common Pleas, 1780 March; No. 2003
- State of Massachusetts Bay, Council to Daniel Waters, 1779 July; No. 2004
- Chauveau Masson and Company to Thomas Mumford, 1781 June 30; No. 2005
- Stamp Act, 1765 August-1766 May 19; No. 2006
- John Mease to Jasper Yeates, 1780 April 4; No. 2007
- Christopher Meng to John Fisher, 1782 June 10; No. 2008
- Phillip Moore and Archibald Mercer to Samuel White, 1778 July 2; No. 2009
- Thomas Minor, 1833 September 21; No. 2010
- James Monroe to Samuel Lewis Southard?, 1826 January 9; No. 2011
- Jonathan Morrill to Reuben Hoyt, n.d.; No. 2012
- Robert Morris to William Cranch, 1795 December 14; No. 2013
- Robert Morris to Jonathan Hudson, 1779 April 8; No. 2014
- Robert Morris to the United States of America, 1782 September 3; No. 2015
- Isaac Moses and Reyne Moses to Rev. Michael Schlatter, 1778 September 28; No. 2016
- Samuel Clark to John DeWitt, Jr., 1778 February 19; No. 2017
- John Neilson to George Washington, 1779 June 5; No. 2018
- New Jersey, Governor (William Livingston) to Elizabeth Stull, 1779 July 16; No. 2019
- New York, Sons of Liberty to the House of Representatives for the Colony of New York, 1765; No. 2020
- N.C. Flagg, Simeon DeWitt, and others, Commissioners of the Canal Fund to the cashier of the New York State Bank, 1834 March 31; No. 2021
- Roger Newberry to Howell Woodbridge, 1782 February 25; No. 2022
- John Nixon to John Nicholson, 1791 November 15; No. 2023
- Abraham Ogier, notary public, 1760 December 12; No. 2024
- By order of Peleg Peck to ________, 1778 January 10; No. 2025
- William Osborn to Thomas Hope, 1784 October 15; No. 2026
- Benjamin Page to Lt. ______ Robinson, 1784 April 28; No. 2027
- John Parish to the Officers of His Majesty's Ordnance, 1782 February 2; No. 2028
- William Park to Eleanor Park, 1778 August 26; No. 2029
- Shays' Rebellion, 1787; No. 2030
- Samuel Holden Parsons to Andrew Huntington, 1778 January 2; No. 2031
- Rembrandt Peale to John Murphy, 1826 February 2; No. 2032
- Nathan Pendleton, on behalf of Peleg Pendleton to Joshua Huntington, 1781 March 29; No. 2033
- John Penn, 1765 December; No. 2034
- Plunket Fleeson, 1777 August 14; No. 2035
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor (Thomas Mifflin) to John Nicholson, 1794 July 13; No. 2036
- State of Pennsylvania, Treasurer (David Rittenhouse) to John Hart, 1779 December 6; No. 2037
- Colony of Pennsylvania, Westmoreland County, 1765; No. 2038
- Sarah Peters to Richard Peters, 1794 November 16; No. 2039
- M.A. Pie to Mrs. _______, 1808 January 29; No. 2040
- Sir Robert Pigot to Mrs. _____ Wagner, 1778 January 17; No. 2041
- Enoch Poor, 1778 February-1779 January; No. 2042
- Edmund Quincy to Dorothy Quincy Hancock, 1776 May 25; No. 2043
- Edmund Quincy to Katherine Quincy, 1777 January 24; No. 2044
- Edmund Quincy to John Hancock, 1776 February 8; No. 2045
- Luke Ramson to John Fisher, 1781 November 8; No. 2046
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1800 June 26; No. 2047
  See also Nos. 1826 and 2315.
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1800 July 24; No. 2048
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1800 September 5; No. 2049
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1800; No. 2050
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1802 January 3; No. 2051
- Virginia, City of Richmond to Henry Augustine Washington, 1844 August 8; No. 2052
- James Roosevelt to John DeWitt, Jr., 1783 January 31; No. 2053
- David Ross to a member of the Board of the Council of the State of Virginia, 1781 August 1; No. 2054
- Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1798 July-1806 April; No. 2055
- Thomas Russell to William Augustine Washington, 1785 April 5; No. 2056
- Comfort Sage to Thomas Mumford, 1778 March 11; No. 2057
- West Indies, St. Eustatius, Governor (John DeWindt), 1770 January 3; No. 2058
- Antoine-Raymond-Jean-Gualbert-Gabriel de Sartine, comte d'Alby to Pierre-Francois Cornic Dumoulin, 1777 August 24; No. 2059
  See also Nos. 1850, 1991, and 2060-2061.
- Antoine-Raymond-Jean-Gualbert-Gabriel de Sartine, comte d'Alby to Pierre-Francois Cornic Dumoulin, 1777 December 10; No. 2060
- Antoine-Raymond-Jean-Gualbert-Gabriel de Sartine, comte d'Alby to Pierre-Francois Cornic Dumoulin, 1777 December 13; No. 2061
- Philip Schuyler, on behalf of himself and Robert, Henry, and James Van Rensselaer to Henry Livingston, 1786 January 14; No. 2062
- Philip Schuyler to Joseph Trumbull, 1777 June 29; No. 2063
- Shays' Rebellion, 1786-1787; No. 2064
- Jesse Simms to George Washington, 1798 January 8; No. 2065
- David Smith to Rev. Mark Leavenworth, 1778 October 13; No. 2066
- Hugh Smith to Bushrod Washington, 1810 September 25; No. 2067
- James Smith to William Hartshorne, 1787 June 1; No. 2068
- Society of the Cincinnati to Richard Humphrey Greaton, 1784 May 5; No. 2069
- Society of Friends, accounts of sufferings, 1776-1799; No. 2070
- Society of Friends, meeting for sufferings, 1773 February 26; No. 2071
- Society of Friends to the President (William Moore), Executive Council, and General Assembly of Pennsylvania, 1781 December 6; No. 2072
- Thomas B. Spence to Mrs. Thomas Mann Johnson, 1843 April 15; No. 2073
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben, 1782 January 18,19; No. 2074
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to John "Laurens" Lawrence?, 1784 July 24; No. 2075
- Nathaniel Stevens, 1781 July 22; No. 2076
- Thomas Sthreshly to William Augustine Washington, 1788 February 11; No. 2077
- Luke Stoutenburgh to Joseph Burroughs, 1781 July 19; No. 2078
- Philip Cortlandt, by order of Gen. John Sullivan, 1776 May 18; No. 2079
- John Sullivan to William Greene, 1778 August 23; No. 2080
- John Sullivan to Thomas Mumford, 1766 December 4; No. 2081
- John Sullivan to Thomas Mumford, 1776 April 7; No. 2082
- John Sullivan to Joseph Pearson, 1789 November 9; No. 2083
- State of Connecticut, Governor (Jonathan Trumbull) to Jacob B. Witter, 1800 May 14; No. 2084
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jabez Huntington, 1776 August 7; No. 2085
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jabez Huntington and David Mumford, 1778 June 17; No. 2086
- State of Connecticut, Governor (Jonathan Trumbull), 1779 October 9; No. 2087
- Colony of Connecticut, Governor (Jonathan Trumbull), 1775 July; No. 2088
- Jonathan Trumbull, Jr. to Andrew Huntington, 1782 March 27; No. 2089
- Joseph Trumbull to Jabez Huntington, 1776 August 19; No. 2090
- Rasha Trunel to William Augustine Washington, 1804 March 30; No. 2091
- Shays' Rebellion, 1787 February 19, 20, 21; No. 2092
- State of Connecticut, Pay-Table Office to John Lawrence, 1784 June 1; No. 2093
- Isaac Phillips, 1779 August 23; No. 2094
- United States, Continental Congress (Charles Thomson, secretary), 1774 September 22; No. 2095
- John Hancock to the commanding officer in New Jersey, 1776 November 14; No. 2096
- United States, Continental Army, Quartermaster Department, 1782 November 7-1784 October 28; No. 2097; 1.0 vol.
- United States, Continental Congress (Charles Thomson, secretary), 1779 March 5; No. 2098
- United States, Port of Philadelphia, 1806 October 22; No. 2099
- United States, President (Thomas Jefferson) to Joel Wright, 1808 January 15; No. 2100
- George Washington to George Walton, 1789 June 8; No. 2101
- Benjamin Lincoln to Alexander Galbreath, 1783 June 27; No. 2102
- United States, Secretary of War (James McHenry), 1798 January 1; No. 2103
- William Witherel, 1680?; No. 2104
- David Valentine to John Bowman, 1783 August 29; No. 2105
- David Van Horne, 1773 December-1775 September; No. 2106
- Goose Van Schaick to Maria Ten Broeck Van Schaick, 1778 October 1; No. 2107
- Nathaniel Wales, Jr. to Thomas Mumford, 1779 July 14; No. 2108
- Benjamin Walker to Henry Jackson, 1783 January 28; No. 2109
- John Wall to Tench Francis, 1787 August 31; No. 2110
- Richard Warner, on behalf of Gilbert Livingston to Peter DeWitt, and others, 1780 July 23; No. 2111
- James Warren to Nathaniel Freeman, 1777 February 13; No. 2112
- James Warren to Nathaniel Freeman, 1778 March 25; No. 2113
- James Warren to Elbridge Gerry, 1785 October 4; No. 2114
- Ezekiel Forman Chambers and George Corbin Washington to Samuel Lewis Southard, 1828 January 21; No. 2115
- Bushrod Washington to William Augustine Washington, n.d.; No. 2116
- Bushrod C. Washington to ________, 1835 October 7; No. 2117
- Bushrod Washington to Andrew Reid, 1810 December 17; No. 2118
- Bushrod Washington to Mrs. Elizabeth Whiting, 1797 July 18; No. 2119
- Henry Lee and Bushrod Washington, No. 2120
- James W. Colquhoun, on behalf of Judge Bushrod Washington to George Lewis, 1803 June 8; No. 2121
- Thomas Irwin, 1794 October-1795 June; No. 2122
- Corbin Washington to his uncle George Washington, 1789 December 18; No. 2123
- George Washington to the Commissioners of the Federal City, 1799 August 7; No. 2124
- Jared Sparks to Miss ______ Whitwell, 1863 November 5; No. 2125
- George Washington to John West, Jr., 1775 September 22; No. 2126
- George Washington to John Anderson, 1783 June 9; No. 2127
- Augustine Washington to Lawrence Washington, 1752 June 19; No. 2128
- George Washington for ______, 1777 September 25; No. 2129
- George Washington to William Alexander, Lord Stirling, 1778 November 1; No. 2130
- George Washington to William Alexander, Lord Stirling, 1779 September 13; No. 2131
- George Washington to Dr. James Anderson, 1794 May 26; No. 2132
- George Washington to Burges Ball and Charles Carter, Jr., 1789 October 18; No. 2133
- George Washington to Burges Ball, 1794 July 18; No. 2134
- George Washington to Burges Ball, 1794 September 25; No. 2135
- George Washington to Andrew Elliott Belknap, 1798 October 8; No. 2136
- George Washington to Theodorick Bland, 1781 June 7; No. 2137
- George Washington to Rev. Jonathan Boucher, 1768 August 19; No. 2138
- George Washington to Elias Boudinot, 1779 February 27; No. 2139
- George Washington to Elias Boudinot, 1793 November 27; No. 2140
- George Washington to Daniel Brodhead, 1779 March 5; No. 2141
- George Washington to John Carlisle, Michael Gilbert, John Hughes, and Joseph Lewis, 1780 September 16; No. 2142
- George Washington to Edward Carrington, 1799 December 2; No. 2143
- George Washington to Robert Cary and Company, 1766 March 28; No. 2144
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1776 June 20; No. 2145
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1777 March 3; No. 2146
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1778 September 25; No. 2147
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1780 May 18; No. 2148
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1778 October 18; No. 2149
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1778 October 25; No. 2150
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1778 November 27; No. 2151
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1779 February 22; No. 2152
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1780 November 29; No. 2153
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1781 February 20; No. 2154
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1781 April 12; No. 2155
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1781 May 18; No. 2156
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1781 July 6; No. 2157
- George Washington to Jacques Cole-Mountflorence, 1779 September 28; No. 2158
- George Washington to the commanding officer of Gen. John Stark's Brigade, 1780 February 11; No. 2159
- George Washington to Adam Comstock, 1777 February 2; No. 2160
- George Washington to Francis Corbin, 1798 July 24; No. 2161
- George Washington to the Council of Massachusetts Bay, 1780 September 12; No. 2162
- George Washington to John Cropper, 1799 June 17; No. 2163
- George Washington to Bartholomew Dandridge, 1797 April 3; No. 2164
- George Washington to Elias Dayton, 1781 February 7; No. 2165
- George Washington to Elias Dayton, 1781 August 18; No. 2166
- George Washington to Jonathan Dayton, 1782 May 21; No. 2167
- George Washington to James Duane, 1780 December 26; No. 2168
- George Washington to Benjamin Dulany, 1782 March 15; No. 2169
- George Washington to Oliver Evans, 1798 April 8; No. 2170
- George Washington to George William Fairfax, 1773 October 15; No. 2171
- George Washington to Mrs. Jane Donaldson Fairfax, 1799 July 4; No. 2172
- George Washington to John Fitzgerald, 1786 September 9; No. 2173
- George Washington to Elbridge Gerry, 1777 September 27; No. 2174
- George Washington to Elbridge Gerry, 1781 February 20; No. 2175
- George Washington to John Taylor Gilman, 1789 September 28; No. 2176
- George Washington to Rev. William Gordon, 1777 June 29; No. 2177
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1780 January 22; No. 2178
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1781 October 6; No. 2179
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1781 December 15; No. 2180
- George Washington to William Hamilton, 1784 January 15; No. 2181
- George Washington to William Hamilton, 1784 April 6; No. 2182
- George Washington to William Hamilton, 1797 March 6; No. 2183
- George Washington to Edward Hand, 1778 October 21; No. 2184
- George Washington to Edward Hand, 1783 July 4; No. 2185
- George Washington to William B. Harrison, 1779 March 5; No. 2186
- George Washington to Maj. ______ Howell, 1778 February 17; No. 2187
- George Washington to Henry Jackson, 1778 June 18; No. 2188
- George Washington to Henry Jackson, 1779 November 28; No. 2189
- George Washington and Martha Washington to Don Jose de Jaudenes, 1794 April 11; No. 2190
- George Washington to John Jay, 1785 September 27; No. 2191
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1779 November 12; No. 2192
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1783 September 25; No. 2193
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1787 March 8; No. 2194
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1789 January 29; No. 2195
- George Washington to Henry Laurens, 1778 October 3; No. 2196
- George Washington to Henry Laurens, 1779 September 29; No. 2197
- George Washington to John Laurens, 1782 March 22; No. 2198
- George Washington to Henry Lee, 1788 December 23; No. 2199
- George Washington to Lawrence Lewis, 1798 December 2; No. 2200
- George Washington to Lawrence Lewis, 1799 September 28; No. 2201
- George Washington to Robert Lewis, 1795 July 27; No. 2202
- George Washington to Robert Lewis, 1779 January 23; No. 2203
- George Washington to Benjamin Lincoln, 1777 July 24; No. 2204
- George Washington to William Livingston, 1776 July 5; No. 2205
- George Washington to William Livingston, 1782 January 12, 13; No. 2206
- George Washington to William Livingston, 1782 June 18; No. 2207
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1798 September 16; No. 2208
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1799 September 14; No. 2209
- George Washington to Lachlan McIntosh, 1783 December 15; No. 2210
- George Washington to James Madison, 1790 December 11; No. 2211
- George Washington to James Madison, 1792 May 5; No. 2212
- George Washington to Charles Fenton Mercer, 1798 July 25; No. 2213
- George Washington to Thomas Mifflin, 1792 September 29; No. 2214
- George Washington to Stephen Milbourne, 1797 May 15; No. 2215
- George Washington to Robert Morris, 1777 August 14; No. 2216
- George Washington to Jedidiah Morse, 1793 July 17; No. 2217
- George Washington to Sarah Wentworth Apthorp Morton, 1798? January; No. 2218
- George Washington to Thomas Mumford, 1780 September 15; No. 2219
- George Washington to Battaile Muse, 1786 February 4; No. 2220
- George Washington to Battaile Muse, 1786 March 8; No. 2221
- George Washington to Battaile Muse, 1790 December 27; No. 2222
- George Washington to Don Diego Jose Navarro, 1779 March 4; No. 2223
- George Washington to Thomas Nelson, 1781 November 4; No. 2224
- George Washington to Thomas Nelson, 1789 July 27; No. 2225
- George Washington to Joseph Palmer, 1775 August 7; No. 2226
- George Washington to Nathaniel Peabody, 1780 October 26; No. 2227
- George Washington to Charles Willson Peale, 1787 February 16; No. 2228
- George Washington to Richard Peters, 1797 January 21; No. 2229
- George Washington to William Phillips, 1778 November 6; No. 2230
- George Washington to Nathaniel Ramsay, 1777 March 29; No. 2231
- George Washington to Moses Rawlins, 1779 January 30; No. 2232
- George Washington to Joseph Reed, 1780 April 12; No. 2233
- George Washington to Jacob Read, 1784 February 12; No. 2234
- George Washington to George "Read" Reid, 1782 July 10; No. 2235
- George Washington to Daniel Richardson, 1773 December 30; No. 2236
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1779 July 25; No. 2237
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1781 April 25; No. 2238
- George Washington to Israel Shreve, 1795 June 27; No. 2239
- George Washington to William Smallwood, 1777 March 12; No. 2240
- George Washington to Thomas Smith, 1787 September 16; No. 2241
- George Washington to Thomas Smith, 1787 December 3; No. 2242
- George Washington to Alexander Spotswood, 1799 July 31; No. 2243
- George Washington to Richard Sprigg, 1787 April 1; No. 2244
- George Washington to Walter Stewart, 1784 February; No. 2245
- George Washington to David Stuart, 1787 February 12; No. 2246
- George Washington to David Stuart, 1790 March 23; No. 2247
- George Washington to Benjamin Tallmadge, 1779 September 7; No. 2248
- George Washington to William Thompson, 1799 March 18; No. 2249
- George Washington to Tench Tilghman, 1783 October 2; No. 2250
- George Washington to the President of Congress (John Hanson), 1782 January 2; No. 2251
- George Washington to Goose Van Schaick, 1778 October 27; No. 2252
- George Washington to Bushrod Washington, 1797 February 16; No. 2253
- George Washington to George Augustine Washington, 1782 September 25; No. 2254
- George Washington to George Augustine Washington, 1783 September 4; No. 2255
- George Washington to George Augustine Washington, 1793 January 27; No. 2256
- George Washington to Lund Washington, 1776 October 6; No. 2257
- George Washington to Lund Washington, 1782 January 8; No. 2258
- George Washington to Lund Washington, 1793 December 9; No. 2259
- George Washington to Samuel Washington, 1771 December 6; No. 2260
- George Washington to William Augustine Washington, 1799 June 10; No. 2261
- George Washington to Wakelin Welch and Son, 1789 October 13; No. 2262
- George Washington to Alexander White, 1798 September 12; No. 2263
- George Washington to Anthony Whiting, 1791 August 29; No. 2264
- George Washington to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1797 December 17; No. 2265
- George Washington to Robert Cary and Company, 1761 July 14; No. 2266
- George Washington to James Mercer, 1774 January 8; No. 2267
- George Washington to William Smallwood, 1778 June 5; No. 2268
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1781 August 8; No. 2269
- George Washington to David Stuart, 1788 June 27; No. 2270
- George Washington, 1775 April; No. 2271
- George Washington, 1768; No. 2272
- George Washington, 1785; No. 2273
- George Washington, 1782 July 11; No. 2274
- George Washington "to the Friends of America in the State of New Jersey", 1776 December 31; No. 2275
- George Washington for William Baker, 1749 November 10; No. 2276
- George Washington "to the citizens of Savannah and the inhabitants of its vicinity", 1791 May 13; No. 2277
- John West, Jr. and George Washington, 1769 April 29; No. 2278
- George Corbin Washington to Thomas McElderry, 1809 September 13; No. 2279
- Hannah Bushrod Washington to Mrs. _____ Green, n.d.; No. 2280
- Henry Augustine Washington, 1844 November 9; No. 2281
- Regarding Henry Augustine Washington, n.d.; No. 2282
- Henry A. Washington to his father, 1850 January 19; No. 2283
- Henry A. Washington to his father, 1850 March 28; No. 2284
- John Macrae Washington to Nathan Towson, 1823 November 13; No. 2285
- Thomas Jett, 1772; No. 2286
- John A. Washington to Thomas Walker Gilmer, 1832 February 18; No. 2287
- John Augustine Washington to ________, 1775 November; No. 2288
- Lawrence Washington to the cashier of the Farmer's Bank of Virginia in Fredericksburg, 1838 August 28; No. 2289
- Lawrence Washington to the cashier of the Farmer's Bank of Virginia in Fredericksburg, 1838 December 4; No. 2290
- Lawrence Washington to John Gray, 1840 December 18; No. 2291
- Martha Dandridge Custis Washington to Mercy Otis Warren, 1790 June 12; No. 2292
- Martha Dandridge Custis Washington to "Fanny" Francis Bassett Washington, 1792 April 22; No. 2293
- Martha Dandridge Custis Washington to "Fanny" Frances Bassett Washington, 1792 July 1; No. 2294
- P.G. Washington to Robert White, 1853 December 21; No. 2295
- Samuel Washington to George Washington, 1797 July 7; No. 2296
- Henry Bowcock to William Augustine Washington, 1797 June 16; No. 2297
- Ferguson and Gibson Henderson, 1797 August-1798 August; No. 2298
- William Augustine Washington, 1781-1793; No. 2299
- William A. Washington to Augustine Love, 1785 February 23; No. 2300
- William Augustine Washington to William Beverly, 1826 September 10; No. 2301
- William Augustine Washington to George Washington, 1799 July 13; No. 2302
- William Myers, on behalf of Samuel Rogers to William Augustine Washington, 1808 October 5; No. 2303
- William L. Washington to Mountjoy Scholl, 1823 November 13; No. 2304
- William Lanier Washington, 1921 February 11; No. 2305
- Anthony Wayne to the Commissary, 1796 July 25; No. 2306
- Anthony Wayne to Henry Jackson, 1782 May 9; No. 2307
- Anthony Wayne to "Polly" Mary Penrose Wayne, 1780 June 29; No. 2308
- Anthony Wayne to Margaretta Wayne, 1780 June 29; No. 2309
- Samuel Blachley Webb to ________, 1777 March 31; No. 2310
- Oliver Wellington, 1775 October 11; No. 2311